https://urj.org/privacy-statement-terms-of-use

Privacy Statement & Terms of Use
The terms and conditions as defined here apply to all online properties of the Union for Reform Judaism. URJ is firmly committed to maintaining the privacy of visitors to its website and to the privacy of the members of URJ congregations.
Privacy Statement
Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Statement describes the types of information Union for Reform Judaism (“URJ”) collects from and about you when you visit the URJ (“we,” or “our”) website or affiliated websites, listed in Appendix A below, our presence on social media (including Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, Flickr, YouTube, LinkedIn, and Instagram), and any domains and online presences acquired in the future (collectively referred to as the “Site”),
This Privacy Statement, governed by our Terms and Conditions also explains how URJ may use and disclose such information, as well as your ability to control certain uses of it. By using the Site, you agree to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Statement. If you do not, please do not use the Site.
Information Collection
Information You Provide
URJ collects personal information from you when you choose to share it with us. This may include when you use our Site, create an online account with us, create a camp registration profile with us, make a purchase, request information from us, sign up for newsletters or our email list, use our service, participate in a survey or promotion, or otherwise contact us. The personal information we collect may include your name, address, email address, or telephone number. If you register for camp with us or seek to work as a camp staff member, the personal information we collect may include a screen or user name, Instant Messaging User ID, photos, user-uploaded videos, social security number, government-issued ID number (e.g. Driver’s License), date of birth, or personal health information. If you make a purchase from us or make a donation, we may collect a credit/debit card number or other financial information.
Information You Provide Through Social Media
You may be required to provide certain personal information to create your URJ account or to receive certain offers. If you use a third party login to create your account (such as Facebook Connect) or otherwise link to us, we may receive certain information about you from the third party (such as a social network) based on your registration and privacy settings on those third party services.
Information Automatically Collected
We may use cookies, HTML tracking information, or other technologies to collect certain information about visitors to our Site and interactions with our emails and online advertisements, and to allow URJ to keep track of analytics and certain statistical information which enables URJ to improve its Site and provide you with more relevant content and advertising on our Site and other sites.
For example, we may automatically collect certain non-personal information from you, including but not limited to your browser type, device type, operating system, unique device identifier of any of your computer(s) or device(s) that are used to access the Site, software version, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, geolocation, phone model, phone operating system, and the domain name from which you accessed the Services. We also may collect information about your use of the Site, including the date and time you visit the Site, the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing or using the Site, the number of times you return to the Site, other click-stream or site usage data, emails that you open, forward or click-through to our Site, and other sites that you may visit.
Third Party Service Providers
We may use third party service providers to support our Site or Apps. Some of these service providers may use technology such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, or Flash cookies to receive, collect, and store information on our behalf.
Third Party Analytic Technologies
Our third party analytics and advertising service providers may also use technology such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, or Flash cookies. We use third party analytics and advertising tools (including Google Analytics, Bing Webmaster Tools, Facebook’s Marketing APIs, Twitter Analytics, YouTube Analytics, and Sprinklr) that may automatically collect non-personal information from you when you interact with our Site, advertising, and social media. The Google Analytics features we use include Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick Platform Integrations, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. This non-personal information is collected through the use of first party cookies, third party cookies, and web beacons. The information collected may include IP address, the website you came from (known as the referring URL), the type of browser, device and operating system you use, the time and date of access, the pages you visit within our Site (and the order in which you visit them), geographic information, and other information that does not personally identify you. This information may be collected by and shared with our third party analytics and advertising service providers, including Google, Bing, Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, and Sprinklr. These allow URJ, and our third party analytics and advertising service providers, to collect non-personal information about you and your use of our Site, advertising and social media.
Information Collected From Other Sources
We may obtain information about you from other sources, including social networks that you use to connect with URJ. This information may include name, user name, demographic information, updated address or contact information, interests, and publicly-observed data, such as from social media and online activity.
Combination of Information
We may combine the information we receive from and about you, including information you provide to us and information we automatically collect through our Site, as well as information across other computers or devices that you may use, and from third party sources.
Tracking Options and California Do Not Track Disclosures
Certain parts of our Site require cookies. You are free to set your browser or operating system settings to limit certain tracking or to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Site or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Please refer to your Web browser’s or operating system’s website or “Help” section for more information on how to delete and/or disable your browser or operating system from receiving cookies or controlling your tracking preferences.
Our system may not respond to Do Not Track requests or headers from some or all browsers. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, click here and here.
Information Use
URJ may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes:
To respond to your inquiries, contact, and communicate with you;
To process payment card transactions for services you purchased from us;
To enable camp registrations for campers and camp staff;
To contact you with information, newsletters and promotional materials from URJ or on behalf of our partners and affiliates
To review the usage and operations of our Site and improve our content and services;
To provide you with customized Site content on the Site, or via email;
To contact you with information, newsletters and promotional materials from URJ or on behalf of our partners and affiliates;
To contact you when necessary;
To use your data in an aggregated non-specific format for analytical and demographic purposes;
To address problems with the Site or our business;
To protect the security or integrity of the Site;
As otherwise described to you at the point of data collection; and
To use and disclose your credit/debit card information only to process payments and prevent fraud
Additionally, if you use the Site to connect with third party services you authorize us to use information from and about you, on your behalf, to interact with these third party services based on your requests.
Information Sharing
URJ may disclose the information we collect from and about you as follows: (1) with affiliated organizations; (2) to our third party service providers that provide business, professional or technical support functions for us, including to the extent necessary or desirable to complete your transaction; (3) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of the URJ Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (4) to respond to judicial process or provide information to law enforcement or regulatory agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; and (5) as described to you at the point of collection.
URJ may also share aggregate or anonymous non-personal information with third parties for their marketing or analytics uses.
Also, URJ may sell or purchase assets during the normal course of our business. If another entity acquires us or any of our assets, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity. In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use personal information provided through this Site in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Statement.
Service Providers
URJ may contract with third party service providers to perform functions related to the Site. These service providers will have access to your information needed to perform their business functions, but we do not permit them to use or share that information for other purposes.
Links to Other Websites
The Site may have links to third-party websites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the practices of such sites.
Public Forums
Any information you may disclose on our Site, in blogs, on message boards, in chat rooms, or on other public areas on the Site or other third-party websites that this Site may link to, becomes public information. Please exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these public areas.
Children's Privacy
Protecting children’s privacy is important to us. We do not direct the Site to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen. If URJ learns that a child under the age of thirteen has provided personally identifiable information to the Site, it will use reasonable efforts to remove such information from its files.
Data Security
We have taken certain physical, administrative, and technical steps to safeguard the information we collect from and about our customers and Site visitors. While we make every effort to help ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee our security measures.
When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card information) on our forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).
Data Storage
Your personal information is stored on servers in the United States; however, some of our brands, subsidiaries, organizations, and Service Providers may store information on servers hosted in other countries. As such, your personal information may be subject to the laws of other countries, where the data protection and other laws may differ from those of the United States. Your personal information may be disclosed in response to inquiries or requests from government authorities or to respond to judicial process in the countries in which we operate.
Access to Your Personal Information
To update your information stored by URJ, you may sign in to your account and update your personal information.
If You Have Questions
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or the practices described herein, you may contact us at 212-650-4000 or urj@urj.org.
User's Acceptance of This Privacy Statement
By visiting the Site, you signify your acceptance to the terms of URJ’s Privacy Statement. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Statement, please do not use the Site.
Revisions to This Statement
URJ reserves the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, remove, or otherwise revise portions of this Privacy Statement at any time. When we do, we will post the change(s) on the Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes. If we change the Privacy Statement in a material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you.
Effective Date: June 2, 2017
Appendix A:
Websites:
Urj.org
ReformJudaism.org
ReformJudaismmag.org
Ccrj.ca
Rac.org
Urjyouth.org
NFTY.org
Jacobscamp.org
Terms of Use
Please read these terms of use carefully before using this site, as they affect your legal rights and obligations including, but not limited to, waivers of rights, limitation of liability, and your indemnity to us.
Please note: these terms of use contain a class action waiver. The waiver affects how disputes with the Union for Reform Judaism are resolved. By accepting these terms of use, you agree to be bound by the waiver. Please read it carefully.
1. Acceptance
By visiting and using the Union for Reform Judaism (“URJ,” “we,” or “our”) website or affiliated websites, listed in Appendix A below, our presence on social media (including Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, Flickr, YouTube, LinkedIn, and Instagram), and any domains and online presences acquired in the future (collectively referred to as the “Site”), you agree, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by these terms and conditions of use (“Terms of Use”), and the URJ Privacy Statement (“Privacy Statement”). If you do not agree to all of these Terms of Use, and the Privacy Policy, do not use this Site.
The URJ may revise these Terms of Use at any time. Your continued usage of this Site will mean you accept those changes, and you will comply with all applicable laws and regulations. The materials provided on this Site are protected by law, including, but not limited to, United States copyright laws and international treaties.
The terms “you,” “your,” “User,” and “Users,” as used herein, refer to all individuals and/or entities accessing this Site for any reason.
2. Use Restrictions
The content on this Site, such as text, graphics, images, photographs, illustrations, trademarks, trade names, service marks, logos, information obtained from the URJ's licensors, and other materials (“Contents”) is protected by copyright under both United States and foreign laws. Title to the Contents remains with the URJ. Any use of the Contents not expressly permitted by these Terms of Use is a breach of these Terms of Use and may violate copyright, trademark, and other laws. Except as stated herein, none of the Contents may be copied, reproduced, distributed, republished, downloaded, displayed, posted or transmitted in any form or by any means without the prior written permission of the URJ or its licensors.
The URJ authorizes its Member Congregations, which are defined as those congregations listed in the online congregational directory, to view and download and print a single copy of the Contents on either URJ.org or ReformJudism.org, with the exception of the Torah Translations, solely for the Member Congregations’ own lawful, personal, non-commercial use and must include attribution and links as well as the following copyright notice: “Copyright © 2017, URJ. All rights reserved” and retain other copyright and proprietary rights notices which were contained in the Contents.
Torah Translations are provided on our site courtesy of the Central Conference of American Rabbis. No part of this translation may be reproduced, stored in a retrieval system, distributed, or be transmitted without express written permission from the Central Conference of American Rabbis (“CCAR“). For permission, please contact CCAR Press at info@ccar.oeg.
Torah Translations include:
Translation from The Torah: A Modern Commentary, copyright (c) 2016 by CCAR Press. All rights reserved.
Translation of Exodus, Leviticus Numbers Deuteronomy from NJPS © 1962, 1985, 1999; CJPS © 2006. Used and adapted by CCAR Press with permission from The Jewish Publication Society and the University of Nebraska Press.
All other Users who are not Member Congregations may not distribute or repost our content unless they receive written permission. The URJ provides permission on a case-by-case basis with the stipulation that the content must include credit and link back as specified.
Content on all other sites may be downloaded or printed for personal use only. Written permission is required for any other use.
The use of the Contents on any other site or in a networked computer environment for any purpose is prohibited. All rights not expressly granted herein are reserved to the URJ and its licensors. If you violate any of these Terms of Use, your permission to use the Contents automatically terminates and you must immediately destroy any copies you have made of any portion of the Contents.
3. User Submissions
The personal information you submit to the URJ is governed by the URJ's Privacy Policy. To the extent there is an inconsistency between the Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy, the Privacy Policy shall govern. The guidelines for submitting Content is detailed under Submission Guidelines.
Except as provided under Submission of Ideas (below), the URJ does not claim ownership of any information or material a User provides to the URJ or posts, uploads, input, submits, or transmits to this Site (“Submission”). The URJ is not responsible for the accuracy of the content of anything posted as a Submission other than posts signed by members of the URJ staff in their official, professional capacities. You agree that you will not make any Submission that is, in whole or in part, libelous; scandalous; inflammatory; discriminatory; defamatory; false; threatening; vulgar; obscene; pornographic; profane; abusive; harassing; invasive of another’s privacy; hateful or bashing, aimed at gender, race, color, sexual orientation, national origin, religious views, or disability; in violation of local, state, national, or international law; or that infringes on, or violates, any right of any party. Additionally, you agree that you will not: (a) make any Submission that is an advertisement or solicitation of business; (b) disrupt the normal flow of dialogue or make a Submission unrelated to the topic being discussed (unless it is clear the discussion is free-form); (c) post a chain letter or pyramid scheme; impersonate another person; (d) distribute viruses or other harmful computer code; (e) harvest or otherwise collects information about others, including email addresses, without their consent; (f) post the same note more than once or “spamming”; or (g) engage in any other conduct that restricts or inhibits any other person from using or enjoying the Site, or which, in the judgment of the URJ, exposes the URJ or any of its licensors, partners, or customers to any liability or detriment of any type.
By making a Submission, you agree that such Submission is non-confidential, non-proprietary, and may be disseminated or used by the URJ. If you make a Submission, you automatically grant—or warrant that the owner of such content has expressly granted—the URJ a royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, worldwide nonexclusive license to use, reproduce, create derivative works from, modify, publish, edit, translate, distribute, perform, and display the Submission in any media or medium, or any form, format, or forum now known or hereafter developed. Notwithstanding the foregoing, the URJ is not required to use any Submission.
You are solely responsible for your Submission, the consequences of making a Submission, and your reliance on any Submissions. The URJ is not responsible for the consequences of any Submission. The URJ is not responsible for screening or monitoring Submissions made to this Site by Users. If notified by a User of a Submission allegedly in violation of these Terms of Use, the URJ may investigate the allegation and determine in good faith and its sole discretion whether to remove such Submission. The URJ will have no liability or responsibility to Users for performance or nonperformance of such activities.
The URJ reserves the right (but is not obligated) to: (a) record the dialogue on the Site; (b) investigate an allegation that a Submission does not comply with these Terms of Use and determine in its sole discretion to remove or request the removal of the Submission; (c) remove Submissions which are abusive, illegal, disruptive, or outdated, or that otherwise fail to comply with these Terms of Use; (d) terminate a User’s access to any or all parts of the Site upon any breach of these Terms of Use or the law; (e) monitor; edit for grammar, punctuation, style and editorial flow; or disclose any Submission; (f) edit or delete any Submission posted on the Site, regardless of whether such Submission violates these Terms of Use. We occasionally will return a Submission to its author to suggest changes, omissions, and/or additions that our editing team deems necessary to strengthen the post such that it may become appropriate for publishing on our blog(s).
4. Comments on Site Content
The URJ encourages comments on its blogs, websites, and social media sites (“Comments”). We review all Comments before they're posted and will not publish those Comments that are off-topic, promote a commercial product, or veer outside of the boundaries established herein. We expect the Comments to adhere to a basic level of civility, allowing for mutually respectful disagreements.
By posting any Comments on any URJ Site, you give the URJ the irrevocable right to reproduce, distribute, publish, display, edit, modify, create derivative works from, and otherwise use your Comment for any purpose in any form and on any media. You also agree that you will not: post material that infringes on the rights of any third party, including intellectual property, privacy or publicity rights; post material that is illegal, obscene, sexually explicit, defamatory, threatening, harassing, abusive, slanderous, hateful, or embarrassing to any other person or entity as determined by the URJ in its sole discretion; post advertisements, solicitations of business, or political endorsements; post chain letters or pyramid schemes; impersonate another person; or post the same note more than once or”spam.”
The URJ reserves the right but is under no obligation to do any or all of the following: remove communications that are abusive, illegal or disruptive, or that otherwise fail to conform with these Terms of Use; terminate a User's access to any Site feature upon any breach of these Terms of Use; or edit or delete any communications posted on any Site feature, regardless of whether such communications violate these standards.
The URJ has the absolute right to monitor and edit or remove any activity or Content, for any reason. The URJ reserves the right to ban visitors who post unacceptable Comments or Content from posting Comments in the future. Comments posted are not the opinion of the URJ, and the URJ takes no responsibility and assumes no liability for any comments posted by you or any third party.
The Union for Reform Judaism reserves the right to terminate the commenting feature at any time, with or without advanced notice.
5. Liability of the URJ and Its Licensors and Partners
The use of the Site or the Contents is at your own risk. The Contents in this Site could include technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. The URJ may make changes or improvements at any time.
THE CONTENTS IN THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, THE URJ DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. THE URJ DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED IN THE MATERIAL WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THIS SITE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES IT AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. THE URJ DOES NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE OF OR THE RESULT OF THE USE OF THE CONTENTS IN THIS SITE IN TERMS OF THEIR CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE. YOU (AND NOT THE URJ) ASSUME THE ENTIRE COST OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION.
THE URJ ASSUMES NO LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT OR TORT, FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, INCLUDING (WITHOUT LIMITATION) DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF ANTICIPATED PROFITS OR REVENUE OR OTHER ECONOMIC LOSS IN CONNECTION WITH OR ARISING FROM ANY ACT OR OMISSION BY THE URJ, ITS AGENTS, AFFILIATES, JOINT VENTURE PARTNERS, INDEPENDENT CONTRACTORS, OR UNAFFILIATED THIRD PARTIES AS A RESULT OF ANY ACT OR OMISSION IN FULFILLMENT OF OR IN BREACH OF THESE TERMS OF USE OR THE PRIVACY POLICY.
6. Your Account
If you use this Site, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your mobile device or computer. You agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password. The URJ reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel orders in its sole discretion.
7. Contact with Third Parties and Third Party Websites
The Site may contain hyperlinks to other websites and webpages (“Third-Party Pages”), as well as to text, graphics, videos, images, music, sounds, and information belonging to or originating from other third-parties (collectively, “Third-Party Applications”).  The URJ does not investigate, monitor, or review any Third-Party Pages or Third-Party Applications to ensure their accuracy, completeness, or appropriateness. The URJ is not responsible for the Third-Party Pages or any Third-Party Applications accessed through the Site. You agree that the URJ shall have no liability with respect to any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of any dealings between you and any third party, or as a result of the presence of such third party on the Site.
The inclusion of any hyperlinks to any Third-Party Pages or Third-Party Applications on the Site does not indicate the URJ’s approval or endorsement thereof. These links are provided solely as a convenience or benefit to Users. Your interactions with a third party on the Site, or based on such third party’s participation or presence on the Site, are solely between you and the third party. The URJ makes no representations or warranties with respect to the content, ownership, or legality of any such linked third party website. If you choose to leave the Site to access any Third-Party Pages or Third-Party Applications, you do so at your own risk.
8. Indemnity
You agree to defend, indemnify, and hold the URJ, its officers, directors, employees, agents, licensors, and partners, harmless from and against any claims, actions, demands, liabilities, and settlements including, without limitation, reasonable legal and accounting fees, resulting from, or alleged to result from, your use of the Site or Contents, or your violation of these Terms of Use or arising out of a claim by a third party relating to the Comments or any material you have posted on the Site.
9. Modification or Suspension of the Site
You agree that the URJ may, in its sole discretion and at any time, modify, discontinue, or suspend its operation of the Site, any part thereof or any Contents, temporarily or permanently, without notice or liability to you.
10. General
The URJ makes no claims that the Contents are appropriate or may be downloaded outside of the United States of America. Access to the Contents may not be legal by certain persons or in certain countries. If you access the Site from outside the United States, you do so at your own risk and are responsible for compliance with the laws of your jurisdiction. The following provisions survive the expiration or termination of these Terms of Use for any reason whatsoever: Liability of the URJ and its Licensors and Partners, Use Restrictions, User Submissions, Submission of Ideas, Indemnity, Applicable Laws, and Complete Agreement.
11. Applicable Laws
These Terms of Use are governed in accordance with the laws of New York, United States of America, without regard to its conflict of law provisions. You and the URJ hereby expressly consent and submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the state and federal courts of New York, New York for the adjudication or disposition of any claim, action or dispute arising out of these Terms of Use. If any provision of these Terms of Use is found to be invalid by any court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of these Terms of Use, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any of these Terms of Use shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or condition or any other term or condition.
If any provision of these Terms of Use is found to be invalid by any court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of these Terms of Use, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any of these Terms of Use shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or condition or any other term or condition.
12. Class Action Waiver
WHERE PERMITTED UNDER THE APPLICABLE LAW, YOU AND THE URJ HEREBY EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT EACH MAY BRING CLAIMS AGAINST THE OTHER ONLY IN YOUR OR ITS INDIVIDUAL CAPACITY AND NOT AS A PLAINTIFF OR CLASS MEMBER IN ANY PURPORTED CLASS OR REPRESENTATIVE ACTION. Unless both you and the URJ agree, no arbitrator or judge may consolidate more than one person’s claims or otherwise preside over any form of a representative or class proceeding.
13. Waiver of Jury Trial; Remedies
You hereby acknowledge and agree that any controversy which may arise under this Agreement is likely to involve complicated and difficult issues and, therefore, you irrevocably and unconditionally waive any right you may have to a trial by jury in respect of any legal action arising out of or relating to this Agreement or the transactions contemplated hereby. The rights and remedies under this Agreement are cumulative and are in addition to and not in substitution for any other rights and remedies available at law or in equity or otherwise.
14. Notice and Take Down Procedures
If you believe any Submission accessible on or from the Site infringes your copyright, you may request removal of those materials (or access thereto) from this Site by contacting the URJ (address identified below) and providing the following information:
Identification of the copyrighted work that you believe to be infringed. Please describe the work, and where possible include a copy or the location (e.g., URL) of an authorized version of the work;
Identification of the Submission that you believe to be infringing and its location. Please describe the Submission, and provide us with its URL or any other pertinent information that will allow us to locate the Submission;
Your name, address, telephone number, and (if available) email address;
A statement that you have a good faith belief that the complained of use of the work is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law;
A statement that the information you have supplied is accurate, and indicating that “under penalty of perjury,” you are the copyright owner or authorized representative; and
A signature or the electronic equivalent from the copyright holder or authorized representative.
Our address for copyright issues relating to this website is as follows:
The Union for Reform Judaism
633 Third Avenue
New York, New York 10017
Urj@urj.org
In an effort to protect the rights of copyright owners, the URJ maintains a policy for the termination, in appropriate circumstances, of Users of this Site who are repeat infringers.
15. Complete Agreement
Except as expressly provided in a particular notice or disclaimer posted by or on behalf of the URJ on this Site, these Terms of Use, including the URJ Privacy Policy, constitute the entire agreement between you and the URJ with respect to the use of the Site and Contents.
Appendix A:
Websites:
